

### **PROFILE**

A highly motivated individual with 5+ years of experience in Sales and Business Development. In the past year, I discovered a passion for Web Development and since then I am honing my technical skills to enable my career shift towards this domain. Aside from that, living and working in multiple countries have helped me develop a high level of intercultural awareness, empathy, and emotional intelligence which further my adaptability and interpersonal skills.

## **PERSONAL DATA**

Phone: +31636084426 Address: Ankaradreef 20

3564VK, Utrecht

Date of birth: 22-04-1987 Place of birth: Al-haska - Syrië E-mail: Rakandouli@gmail.com

# RELEVANT (COMPUTER) SKILLS

- HTML, SCSS, NPM, Git, JS, GSAP, Node.js, Express, React, Redux, Axios API, J-Query.
- Primavera v.6 (Project Management Software)
- Graphic design (Photoshop Adobe
- VD illustrator and Figure )
- XD, illustrator and Figma)
- Sage AccPac 500 ERP v 5.5 (Accountancy and Sales Software)

#### HOBBIES

Drawing, sports, traveling, cultures, football

### **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021: Full Stack JavaScript developer course - by Codaisseur Academy

Dec 2020 - Apr 2021: React.js, Redux, axios course

**Feb 2020 – Nov 2020: (HTML, CSS and JavaScript) courses –** successfully completed multiple courses with the ability to use GSAP, lokomotive, J-Query, SCSS, NPM, GIT

2018 – 2019: IELTS courses and preparation for the exam

2017 - 2018: Babel language course - Dutch language (Level B1 and B2)

2007 – 2011: Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration, Arab International

University (Daraa, Syria) - Specialized in Management

**2007 – 2008: Business administration skills, Syrian Enterprise and Business Center (Damascus, Syria)** – In collaboration with the Syrian Enterprise and Business Center, SME Support Program, and European Training Foundation

## **EXPERIENCE**

Dec 2020- Nu: Freelance web-developer 808-Studio – Word-press theme development

- Webdesign/ front-end development using: PHP, LESS, Vanille JS/ QUERY.
- Building and integrating Search engine optimization.

Jan 2017 – Jan 2018: Seller at Zara (Utrecht) – Present and sell products using solid arguments to customers

Jan 2015 – July 2015: Graphic designer and translator, Gökkuşağı (Istanbul, Turkey)

- Designed posters, flyers and brochures
- Created Arabic language Facebook page
- Translated content from English to Arabic

May 2014 – Oct 2014: Logistics employee, Target med Int. (Amman, Jordan)

Managed logistic exports to Iraq

Jan 2013 - May 2014 Account manager, United Mining Industries (Amman, Jordan)

- Managed over 50+ customer accounts and solved problems regarding payment, account statements, expenses and invoices
- Managed inventory data (packing lists, monthly quantities) with Sage account software. Which led to 50% increase in the productivity of our team
- Created a monthly report for all the regional office sales

Jan 2012 – Dec 2012: Sales Promoter, Toshiba (Amman, Jordan)

Managed Toshiba televisions section, Won the best tv Seller of the month (may)

April 2011 – July 2011 Manager Assistant/Intern, Nabeel Nafieseh (Damascus, Syria)

- Studied the company structure (including SWOT analysis)
- Implementation of a new distribution system

2010 - 2011 Cashier, Nabeel Nafieseh (Damascus, Syria)

## **VOLUNTEER WORK**

2018 - Present Voluntary Arabic Language Coach at De Voorkamer

• Teaching Arabic and creating study materials

2016 - 2017 Relocation volunteer

• Helped families and the elderly move from the AZC to their own homes

2015 – 2016 Arabic-English Translator in AZCs throughout the Netherlands

2006 – 2011 Volunteer employee, The Circassian Foundation

• Organized social events for the Circassian community

## **LANGUAGES**

Arabic: Native language English: IELTS Band 6

Dutch: Level B2, limited working proficiency.

Turkish: Level A2, Basic user,

## **CONTACT LINKS**

Portfolio: https://www.rdouli.online/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakandouli/

GitHub: https://github.com/Rairakzak